

Veysi ADIN

Date of birth: 17/02/1998

Nationality: Turkish

Gender: Male

CONTACT

5 Hwarang-ro 14-gil, Wolgok 2(i)-dong, Seongbuk-gu, KIST Dormitory B Room No:307 02792 Seoul, South Korea

veysi.adin@outlook.com

(+82) 1042880217

https://veysiadn.github.io/

LinkedIn: https://
www.linkedin.com/in/
veysiadn/

ABOUT ME

Hey! It's **Veysi ADIN, and** I'm a **Junior Embedded System Engineer** located in Seoul, South Korea. I'm a master student at University of Science and Technology (UST), I will be graduating on August 2022, and currently I'm working at Korea Institute of Science and Technology (KIST) campus as a research assistant. My main focus is on development of control framework for robotic applications, software safety and fieldbus protocols. I enjoy electronics, DIY projects and learning new things every day. I like to develop applications that solve real life problems.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/09/2020 - CURRENT - Seoul, South Korea

AI & Robotics Master

University of Science and Technology / Korea Institute of Science and Technology

4.33/4.5 | Development of Medical Device Control Software Framework | https://ust.ac.kr/eng.do

01/09/2015 - 24/05/2019 - Mersin, Turkey

Electrical & Electronics Engineer

Mersin University

3.67/4 | Wi-Fi Controlled Natural Gas Valve System With Android Based Software

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/09/2020 - CURRENT - Seoul, South Korea

Research Assistant

Korea Institute of Science and Technology

I worked on development of control framework for medical robots, using EtherCAT protocol based on CiA402 standard and ROS2 as a middleware running on real-time Linux. As a use case for this control framework, we tested our framework on spine surgery robot being developed in Healthcare Robotics Center.

- I designed several PCBs, including safety watchdog PCB, and a flexible PCB for measuring force on the tip of attached instrument to spine surgery robot.
- Worked on safety and verification of medical robot and medical robot software complying various standards, including IEC62304, IEC60601-1/2, ISO 13485.

06/01/2020 - 31/08/2020 - Seoul, South Korea

R&D Intern

Korea Institute of Science and Technology

During this internship, I worked with a start-up company to implement control software and initial prototype of a medical device called microdebrider, which is used in endoscopic sinus surgeries.

Throughout this project, I used:

- ° C++
- o Ot
- ∘ CiA402
- ∘ Git
- EPOS Linux Library
- Doxygen
- Raspberry Pi
- CAN Protocol
- EasyEDA (for custom PCB design)
- SolidWorks (for prototype case design)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Kurdish | Turkish

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening	Reading	Spoken	Spoken	Writing
C2	C2	production interaction		C2
		C2	C2	

Korean

Listening	Reading	Spoken	Spoken	Writing
B1	B1	production interaction		A2
		B1	B1	

DIGITAL SKILLS

Al / Machine Learning / Deep Learning

Python / Tensorflow / PyTorch / ONNX & ONNX Runtime / Pandas Numpy Scikit-learn Scipy libraries

Embedded System Design

C / C++ / ATMEL / STM32 / CAN / CANopen / Communication Interfaces: UART, SPI, I2C / PCB Design / Proteus / Altium Designer

Software

MATLAB / Qt / Git / Julia / ROS/ROS2 / Real-time Linux **Prototyping Products**

SolidWorks / SMD soldering / Arduino / Raspberry Pi **Others**

LaTeX / EtherCAT / CiA 402 / Motion Control

CONFERENCES AND SEMINARS

> The 17th Asian Conference on Computer Aided Surgery / Virtual Conference

Development of Control Framework for Spine Surgery Robot Using EtherCAT

Abstract—As the more sensors and actuators are used in the robotic systems to provide more features, complexity of the system is increasing. When it comes to medical robotics, it becomes harder to ensure safety and determinism in the system. To deal with increasing complexity and ensure precise periodicity and execution timing for a medical robot, in this paper we report development of EtherCAT master as a part of software framework for spine surgery robot. We implemented a multi-axis controller using open-source EtherCAT master running in real-time preemptive Linux. We evaluated the real-time performance of the system in terms of periodicity, jitter and execution time in our first prototype of spine surgery robot.

https://github.com/veysiadn/veysiadn.github.io/raw/master/assets/pdf/

ACCAS2021 VeysiADIN ChunwooKim.pdf

19/05/2021 – 21/05/2021 > – Seoul, South Korea / Korea Robotics Society

Development of motor control component for medical robot software framework based on EtherCAT

Component based software engineering principles can be applied to the development of a robot software to facilitate the complex development process. This paper reports development of a EtherCAT master as part of a software framework for medical robot. A multi axis motor controller is implemented using an open source EtherCAT master running in preemptive real-time Linux. The real-time performance of the controller is evaluated in terms of periodicity, jitter, and execution time.

https://github.com/veysiadn/veysiadn.github.io/raw/master/assets/pdf/KROS Paper Veysi - Submitted 20210311.pdf

HONOURS AND AWARDS

24/05/2019

Valedictorian of Engineering Faculty – Mersin University Engineering Faculty

I have ranked first among the faculty of engineering students graduating in 2019.

01/09/2016

Scholarship – Vehbi Koc Foundation

18/10/2021

Encouragement Award – Korea Institute of Science and Technology

KIST School organizes Idea Bubling Contents each year, where students implements their ideas related to industry, robotics and AI.

I attented the contest with my project called Portable-Progammable Real-time EtherCAT Master, and I won 3rd place among the 59 student projects.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UaHLfNDjBoc